ufindus.com 2010-11-20

# Ufindus Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how we, Ufindus ("U Find Us, we, us, our"), will use personal data. We will be the data controller of your data for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998.

### Who will have access to your data?

Data will be used by Ufindus in the manner set out below (see "How will we use personal data?").

### What will we collect?

We will collect names, addresses and other details provided by you when you contact us with a question or to obtain a quotation for one of our products or services or you would like a free directory listing.

We may also record information about the way you have used our site, in order to improve the way it operates (see "Cookies"). 

### How will we use personal data?

We only collect the data you provide to us under the "Contact" facility on this website. This includes your name, business name if appropriate, address, e-mail address, telephone number and details of your enquiry. This data will be used to provide the service applied for and may be stored by Ufindus to keep you informed of products and services, which may be of interest to you. This data will not be used other than in the normal course of our business. If you do not wish to receive such information, all you need to do is write to let us know. Your email address will only be used by Ufindus to contact you back and we will not pass your details on to third parties without your consent first.

### Cookies

When you use this website we will log your IP (Internet Protocol) address (this is a unique reference number allocated to a computer when accessing the Internet) and collect basic information about the way you use the site during your visit. This information is used only for site navigation and systems administration purposes.

In certain situations we may use cookies in order to recognise you as a site user and to personalise your visit. A cookie is small file sent to a web browser by a web server. We only use cookies for the purposes stated above and where necessary for the full operation of the website.

You can set your browser to reject cookies but if you do so you will be unable to enjoy full site functionality. 

### Links

For your convenience we have included links on this website to other sites that we believe you may find useful. These websites will each have their own privacy statement, which may differ from ours. Therefore please ensure, when you click on any of our links, that you read the privacy statement located on the website you have selected. Any websites connected with this site are not within our control. 

### Your consent / Information

By using this website, you are saying that you agree to the collection and use of any personal information sent to Ufindus, provided it is used as set out in this Policy.

If we decide to change the Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances it is disclosed.

You have the right to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to correct any inaccuracies in your information.

"The Internet is not a 100% secure medium of communication and, accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted via the Internet. We are not responsible for any damages you, or others, may suffer as a result of the loss of confidentiality of such information".

Communications will be monitored regularly to improve our service and for security and regulatory purposes.

Before you provide us with any personal data about a third party you must obtain the correct authority from the individual(s) concerned and undertake to keep them advised about how their information will be used.
